Max 我终于安排好了新计划表
Okay, Max, I figured out our new schedule.
我也终于弄明白了
And I figured out the cheap toothpaste
咱们用的廉价牙膏原来是护臀霜
we've been using is really diaper cream.
不过它的防皮疹成分清洁了我牙缝里的口香糖
On the plus side, that rash cleared up on my gums.
我们从6点到凌晨2点在餐厅上班
We'll do our diner shift from 6:00 till 2:00,
凌晨2点到4点在这里卖小蛋糕
then sell cupcakes here from 2:00 to 4:00,
然后7点到11点做蛋糕
make the cupcakes in the morning from 7:00 to 11:00,
接着12点到4点去上糕点制作课程
and then pastry school from 12:00 to 4:00.
- 没漏掉什么吧?  - 你漏掉了我们得拉屎和睡觉
- Forget anything?  - Just poopin' and sleepin'.
好吧 那我去重新制订计划
Now, I have to go rewrite the schedule.
来吧 Max 明天是一个大日子
Let's go, Max, you have a huge, huge day tomorrow.
糕点培训班要开学了
First day of pastry school.
千万别跟我说大日子
Stop saying it's huge.
每次我觉得什么东西"大"
Whenever I think something's gonna be huge
到头来发现都是蛋蛋
it just turns out to be all balls.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 兜来兜去
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 初见 桃茜茜 2B小贝 西皮jo
校对: 桃茜茜
我奢侈了一回 把衬衫干洗了
I splurged and had my blouse cleaned.
干洗店的塑料袋子让我想起了以前有钱的日子
Dry cleaning bags remind me of when I had money.
是吗? 它们只让我想起来
Really? They remind me
我妈试图憋死我
of when my mother tried to suffocate me.
这是她自己说的 走吧
Allegedly. Let's go.
等一下 Max 先别走
Wait, wait. Max, you can't go yet.
你得留下来帮我个忙
I need you to stay and help with something.
Han 我说过了... 弯腰使劲摩擦
Han, I told you... it's bend and wipe,
它就会在你的童装裤里挺起来
then up come your big boy pants.
Han说得没错 你先别走
Yeah, Han's right. You can't go.
稍等一会
Stay here a few more minutes.
为什么? 哦
Why? Oh.
难道是要给Max做入学前辅导?
Are we having an intervention for Max?
嘿 小伙伴们
Hey, everybody.
希望我没错过
Oh, I hope I'm not late r Max's
Max的开学惊喜派对
first day of school surprise party.
Sophie 我们还没给她惊喜呢
Sophie, we hadn't surprised her yet.
但她都站在这里了
Oh, but she's right there.
被6你搞砸了 Han
You just blew it, Han.
噢 惊喜派对
Aw, a surprise party.
- 多贴心啊 是吧 Max?  - 我才不信这一套
- Isn't this sweet, Max?  - I don't trust it.
上次Oleg对我大叫"惊喜"的时候
Last time Oleg yelled "surprise" at me,
热狗面包里夹着他的鸡鸡
his penis was on a hot dog bun.
肉食者至爱 披萨驾到
One meat lover's pizza.
肉食者也驾到了
And one meat lover.
Max 来吧 趁热吃
Max, come on. Get it while it's hot.
你来打开盒子
You're opening that box.
哦 谁有10美元
Hm, who's got a ten
给送披萨的帅哥当小费?
to tip the cute pizza delivery guy?
Sophie 他是Luis 日班服务员
Sophie, this is Luis, the day waiter.
哦 你就是Sophie啊
Oh, you're Sophie,
Oleg的前女友
Oleg's ex.
姐们儿 久闻你大名啊
Sister, I know all about you.
哦 是吗?
Oh, do you?
你知道我的一切吗?
Do you know all about me?
我可是他的好朋友
I'm his good friend.
我有点听不清你的口音
You know, I'm having trouble hearing your accent.
你说的是"好朋友" 还是"女朋友"?
Did you say "good friend" or "girlfriend?"
拜托 妈妈 我倒是想
Please, mami. I wish.
我喜欢这段表演
I like the entertainment.
甚至比我朋友Stephanie
It's better than the magician
在她的16岁生日派对上
at my friend Stephanie's 16th birthday
破了处更有意思
that made her virginity disappear.
Max 我们为你骄傲
Max, we're all so proud of you.
明天是你余下生命里崭新的一天
Tomorrow is the first day of the rest of your life.
不妙 又来这一套?
Aw, crap. I gotta do this again?
好吧 但这次我可不要看
All right, but this time, I'm not seeing
"曲线难题"这种励志片
trouble with the curve.
你会成就一番大事的
You are about to do something very big.
没错 人生的一大步
Yes, she is. Such a big step.
对我们俩来说都是
Big step for both of us,
因为我也要用我惊人的商业头脑
'cause I'll be using my business acumen
去办公室打工赚学费
working in the office to help pay the tuition.
嘘 Max才是主角
Shh. I'm talking about Max.
所以大家集资为你
So we all chipped in to get you something
开学的第一天买了份礼物
for your first day of school.
明天也是我的第一天啊
It's my first day too.
Caroline 小点声 我都听不到Han
Caroline, please, I can't hear Han
怎么夸Max了 好吗?
talking about Max, okay?
亲爱的 送给你
Here you go, darling,
一个新书包
a book bag for school.
那么 等这结束之后
So what, then? Is my surprise party
是我的惊喜派对吗?
after this one?
怎么回事?
What is happening?
大家和蔼可亲 而且笑容可掬?
People doing nice things for me and smiling?
难道要把我送给另一个家庭收养?
Am I transferring foster homes again?
里面还有东西
And there's more stuff inside.
这也应该是个惊喜
That was supposed to be a surprise too.
哦 惊喜哟!
Oh. Surprise!
Max 打开看看
Max, open it. Look inside.
对啊 Max 快打开看看里面的开学礼物
Yeah, Max, see what's inside for your big day.
Max要开学了 我也要开学了
Big day for Max. Big day for me as well.
地铁卡? 不是吧
A metrocard? No way.
我送的 任坐哦
From me. Unlimited rides.
哟 任骑吗?
Oh. Unlimited rides?
你的相好是这么说的?
Is that what your tramp stamp says?
我应该生气 不过这段子挺逗
I was gonna get mad, but that was a damn good one.
这是啥? Han的小屋?
What's this? Han's house?
说声"谢谢"就行了
A simple "thank you" would suffice.
谢谢你的小屋 Han
Thank you for your house, Han.
是个铅笔盒 我好喜欢
It's a pencil case, and I love it.
本来我坐在这里 以为你们
And I was sitting here, thinking how you were
忘了明天也是我的大日子
all ignoring my part of the big day.
但是你们送给我一个铅笔盒
And then, you give me this pencil case
证明是我想错了
to use in the office and prove me wrong.
那是给Max的
That's for Max.
你们是不是搞错了?
What the hell is wrong with you people?
Max用不着铅笔盒的
Max doesn't even need pencils.
她是去做烘焙的
She'll be baking.
同时她也会被烘
Well, she'll be baked.
快看看
Take a look.
大麻卷
Joints.
Earl 你真好
Earl, that's so sweet.
这些能让我坚持到课间休息
These should last me till recess.
等等 Sophie的印花厨师服在哪?
Wait, where's the chef's coat Sophie had monogrammed?
Han 这本来是一个惊喜的
Han, that was supposed to be a surprise.
我知道 我是在报复你呢
Oh, I know. Karma's a bitch.
好吧
Oh, well.
给你
Look.
上面有我的名字
My name's on this.
以前唯一写着我名字的
The only thing my name's
就是尿液样本了
ever been on before is a urine sample.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
那个包里没有一样是给我的?
So there is nothing in that bag for me?
一样都没有? 哇
Nothing? Wow.
我连夹着Oleg鸡鸡的热狗面包都没有
I'd even take Oleg's penis in a hot dog bun right now.
我立马呈上
I'll be right back.
- 我要上去  - 请让让
- Getting on.  - Please move.
- 我要上去!  - 请让让!
- Getting on!  - Please move!
- 上去!  - 让开!
- On!  - Move!
- 上去! 上去!  - 让开! 让开!
- On! On!  - Move! Move!
我爱地铁
I love the subway.
这里是个发泄的好地方
It's the perfect place to get out aggression.
我刚往别人的肾揍了一拳
I just punched someone in the kidney.
就是我
It was me.
我知道
I know.
噢 臭死了
Oh, oh, bad smell,
像是有人和油炸鹰嘴豆饼鬼混了一晚
Like someone hooked up with a falafel.
- 就是我  - 我知道
- It was me.  - I know.
- Max  - 抱歉
- Max.  - Sorry.
地铁 飞机 狂舞区 我的最爱
Subways, planes, and mosh pits, I let it ride.
我爱死了衬衫上
I love the smell
这股清新的干洗味
of this fresh, dry-cleaned blouse.
真是太兴奋了
I am so excited
不必穿那件服务员的制服
to be out of that waitress uniform,
重新穿回我这精致的商务服装
and back in my chic business clothes,
还有 去到自己的办公室
And, you know, going to my office,
利用自己的沃顿商学院智慧
where I'll probably save the day
有可能会拯救烂摊子
using some of my Wharton magic.
我更喜欢绝望的你
You know, I think I like you better without hope.
Max 你知道这学费很贵的 对吧?
Max, you know this school is expensive, right?
所以你要端正态度 好吗?
You're going in with a good attitude, right?
不要 Earl送的铅笔就是这用途
No, that's what Earl's pencils are for.
别担心 我会努力的
Don't worry, I'll do my best.
瞧 我还有个书包呢
I mean, look, I have a book bag.
我妈唯一让我带到学校去的
The only thing my mother ever sent me to school with
是一张便条 写着"帮我检查虱子"
was a note that said "check me for lice."
大家都送你礼物 真的很贴心
It was so sweet of everyone to give you that,
即使这害得我一晚都睡不着
even though I didn't sleep all night about it.
而且这东西看着不便宜
And it looks kind of expensive.
看看设计师的标签
Check for a designer label.
为啥? 值钱的是这份心意啊
Why? It's the thought that counts.
啥时心意值钱了?
Since when?
让我瞧瞧
Let me see it.
已经抵达第二大街站
Second avenue station.
这里是第二大街站
This is second avenue.
不 不要 Max!
No, no, no, Max!
天啊 他抢了书包 很好 Max
No, he got the book bag. Good, Max, good.
不要放手
Don't let go.
那要是列车开动了
What if the train starts to leave
然后我的手臂被扯断了呢?
and my arms pop off?
那我还怎么去上糕点学校啊?
How will I go to pastry school?
我就会像那种人 用嘴叼着
I'll be one of those people decorating cookies
奶油袋 去装饰曲奇饼
with a bag in their mouth.
你是恶魔
You are the devil.
恶魔
The devil.
你一无所有
You have nothing.
Max 使劲拉! 从恶魔那里拉出来!
Pull, max, pull! Pull it from the devil!
拉不动 恶魔力气大
Can't. The devil works out.
噢!
Ooh!
我的包
My bag.
我的衬衫
My blouse.
我的大麻
My weed.
很好 瞧 都开始上课了
Oh, great, look. Class has started.
我的新生活已经被毁了
My new life already blows.
看啊 帅哥厨师长在那里
Oh, look. There's chef gorgeous.
我不想让他看到我的狼狈样
I don't want him to see me like this.
我去洗手间看看
I'm gonna go to the restroom and see
能否用冷水把污渍洗掉
If cold water can get out any of the stain.
- 上课吧 Max  - 可是我没有厨师服和书包
- Go, Max.  - But I don't have my chef coat or book bag.
我只知道自己只拥有了几个小时
I know I only had them for a couple of hours,
但这可是我最棒的东西啊
But it was the best part of me.
你没问题的
You'll do great.
首先 帮我个忙 帮我检查一下虱子
First, do me a favor. Check me for lice.
本课程旨在给大家介绍
This course is designed to introduce you
在发酵面包的制作过程中
To the skills and techniques required
所需的技巧与技术
in the production of yeast bread,
酥类面团 奶油冻 泡芙面团
Short pastry doughs, custards, pate a choux,
以及蛋糕面糊
And cake batters.
Max厨师 你迟到了
Chef Max, you are late.
等等 不是10点17分才开始上课吗?
Wait, are sure class doesn't start at 10:17?
抱歉 我在地铁里
Sorry, I got robbed on the subway
(Jerk除了有混蛋的意思 还是人名)
被一个混蛋抢劫了
By some jerk.
嘿 这是在叫我吗
Hey, hey, hey, I'm right here.
我没得选了 我可不想因为这名字
I ran out of options, and I didn't wanna
而被剥夺了上糕点学校的权力
strip my way through pastry school.
这还有得选啊?
That's an option?
(因主厨是法国人 口音比较重 发音不标准)
好了 厨师们 注意力集中
All right, chefs. Let's focus.
他刚才是说他想"中我们"吗?
Did he say he wants to "foke us"?
(污渍更脏了)
Bebe 早上好
Morning, Bebe.
嗨 天啊
Hi. Oh, my god.
你怎么了?
What happened to you?
我该告诉你 我的医生说
And I should tell you my doctor says
我不能从别人口中听到坏消息
I'm not allowed to hear bad news for another month.
抱歉我如此狼狈
I apologize for my appearance.
我们在地铁上被人抢劫了
We got robbed on the subway,
然后又被别人的咖啡撞到了
And then someone hit me with hot coffee.
然后 我去用冷水冲洗这滩污渍
Then, I went to wash cold water on the stain
可是没想到把自己的衬衫
And somehow wound up entering myself
弄得这么湿
in a wet t-shirt contest.
我需要很大的勇气来消化这事
Um, that's a lot of energy for me,
所以我打算在这里
So I'm just gonna need to sit here
静坐一会儿
for a second and be quiet.
我知道我们要安静 我也会这么做的
I know we're being quiet, which I'm all about,
不过这些狗狗很可爱
But cute dogs.
谢谢 这是可卡犬
Oh, thanks. They're cocker spaniels.
是我救了它们
I rescue them.
人们会拯救灰犬
You know, people rescue greyhounds
比特犬 但是大家都把
And pit bulls, but everyone ignores
可卡犬给忽略了
The cocker spaniel.
他们通常会这样想 "太恶心了
They're like, "ew, eye goo.
射杀掉"
Shoot it."
我有三只比特犬
I have three cockers.
你有宠物吗?
Do you have any pets?
我有一只马 叫小栗子
I have a horse, Chestnut.
它是一匹纯种马
He's a thoroughbred.
好了 首先我能做什么呢?
Well, what can I do first?
这是什么?
What's this?
我拿着的是果汁单吗?
Why am I holding a juice menu?
我们每一天都会给学生和员工
Every day, we get fresh-pressed juice
提供鲜榨的果汁
For the students and the staff.
真是太好了
What a treat.
鲜榨果汁绝对是坑钱的
Fresh juice is such a scam
除非是别人买单
Unless someone else is payin'.
我就要三号绿色果汁吧
I'll take the greens number three.
你可以把这写在单子上
Uh-huh, well, put it on the list
顺道把其他果汁一起拿了
When you get the other ones.
什么 你要我去端果汁?
Wait, I'm supposed to get the juice?
天啊 我简直就是坏消息制造器
Oh, boy, it's like I'm a bad news machine.
好的
Oh. Okay.
我很乐意去做 虽然我很意外 不过乐意
Happy to do it. Surprised, but happy.
我能否换上一件
Uh, maybe I could change
这种可爱的厨师服呢
Into one of those cute chef jackets.
Nicholas厨师长只允许糕点厨师
Oh, Chef Nicholas only permits pastry chefs
穿这个服装
To wear these.
但是我不能在头一天上班就让别人
But I can't meet everyone on my first day
看到我这幅模样
Looking like this.
本来就够惨的了
I mean, it's already bad enough
要我去端果汁
I'm the juice girl.
你可以穿我的运动衣
I have some workout clothes you can wear.
别担心 衣服我还没穿过的
Don't worry. I haven't worn them yet.
但我以后还会穿
But I will someday.
嗨 嗨 大家好
Hi. Hi, everyone.
有谁要鲜榨果汁
I'm here to take the fresh juice orders
还有 我原本不是穿这衣服来上班的
And also to say this is not what I came to work in.
我一开始穿的衣服没这么多眼睛
What I came to work in had less eyes.
Caroline 欢迎你
Caroline, welcome.
在办公室工作得顺利吗?
How is it going in the office so far?
很好 而且我绝不是穿这件衣服来上班的
So great, and so not what I came to work in.
我一般穿香奈儿 不是狗狗衣
I'm usually wearing chanel, not le chien.
法语中"狗"的意思
That's "dog" in french.
哦 这在英文里是"鸡巴"的意思
Oh, 'cause it's "dork" in english.
嗯 很开心看到你们俩
Well, it is lovely to see both of your faces.
上课 我们从基础的开始
Class, we start with the basics.
不 不 不 你从后面...
No, no, no, you in the back...
要果汁吗 小姐? 你要从一个
Juice, Miss? Care for a juice
SAT考到1560的人那里点杯果汁吗?
From someone who scored 1560 on her SATs?
你竟然超过了500分?
You can score more than 500?
你到底为啥要穿那个?
Why the hell are you wearing that?
没想到你的胸还可以变得更加悲剧啊
I didn't think your chest could get any sadder.
这是Bebe的
It's Bebe's.
Max 点果汁
Max, taking juice orders
不是我来这里的工作
Is not what I came here to do.
我知道 我要宝石红果汁
I hear you. I'll have the ruby red.
我总是保持边缘部分干净
I always keep the edge clean,
所以当我挤压的时候
So when I'm squeezing it,
不会把奶油
It's not gonna have cream
喷得到处都是
Popping all over the place.
人生箴言
Words to live by.
我就是一塌糊涂
I have the opposite problem.
唷 我的奶油现在正要喷了
Yo, my cream's poppin' right now.
你在干嘛? 你说过
What are you doing? You told me
你会认真上课的
You were gonna take school seriously.
不是我的错 是这家伙带坏我
It's not me. That guy's a bad influence.
看看他
Look at him.
他就像是在欢乐的芝麻街
He looks like someone who sells drugs
卖大麻的
On sesame street.
你会惹麻烦的
You're gonna get in trouble,
而且我才不会穿这个可卡犬的衣服
And I am not wearing a cocker spaniel
你会被撵出课堂的
So you can get kicked out of class.
好吧 听到你说的了
Right. I hear you.
现在 我的果汁在哪儿?
Now, where's my juice?
嘿 Max大厨 看我的本事
Hey, chef Max. Check out my technique.
还附带了恶心声音做奖励
Awesome gross sound bonus.
大厨 如果你觉得很有趣
Chef, if you find this so funny,
(他原意是说抽个烟休息 但是发错音了)
要不你去拿个钱?
why don't you take a fiver?
你们是这样说的吧?
Isn't this how your saying goes?
我可没这么说
I don't have a saying,
如果我说了 更可能会是
But if I did, it'd be more like
"吃喝不算骗"
"eatin' ain't cheatin'."
还有谁发现搞笑的事
Anyone else who finds something hilarious
可以一起去走廊呆着
can also go into the hall.
- Max大厨?  - 不 没啥滑稽的事
- Chef Max? Nope,  - nothing 'ilarious.
继续上课
Teach on.
黄段子讲够了
Enough with the dirty jokes.
(master baker有"烘焙师"和"自慰的面包师"之意)
我们来这儿是要成为"自撸大师"
We are all here to become master bakers.
我在很努力地让自己成为"自撸大师"
Master-baking is something I work really hard at it.
- 成为一个自撸大师  - 我还是去走廊吧
- To be a master baker...  - I'll be in the hall.
- 嗨 我是Deke  - 你是说"怪人"?
- Hi, I'm Deke.  - Did you say "freak?"
- Deke  - 你是说"怪咖"?
- Deke.  - Did you say "geek?"
Deke 就像"大鸡巴"
Deke, as in "big deke."
姐的更大
Mine's bigger.
咱俩应该做黄金拍档
We should be lab partners.
来吧 会很拉风的
Come on. It'll be bitchin'.
Max和Deke 一起做蛋糕
Max and Deke, making cakes.
周日 周日 周日 克里德乐队
Sunday, sunday, sunday, with a special performance
特别表演
By Creed.
好的 打住 打住 打住
Okay, now stop, stop, stop.
姐要当个好学生
I am trying to be a good student,
所以你离我远点
So you just stay away from me.
你是个坏榜样
You are a bad influence.
我讲话一针见血 因为在学校时
And I know I nailed that speech 'cause kids at school
那些小孩总是这么说我的
Used to say it to me all the time.
到点该换卫生巾了吧?
Time to change your tampon?
是的
Yep.
第二天 量还很大
Day two. Serious flow.
杀手腰包 你们部落的斗篷呢?
Killer fanny pack. Where's your tribal poncho?
嗯 我把针放在这儿
Ah, keep my needles in this.
你也是瘾君子?
You're a drug addict too?
天啊 你太吸引人了
God. You are irresistible.
这是... 胰岛素 我有糖尿病
It's... it's insulin. I'm a diabetic.
有糖尿病的糕点师
A diabetic pastry chef.
哇 你比姐还心急找死呢
Wow, you're even more self-destructive than me.
所以糖尿病 是怎么样的?
So diabetes, how is that?
令人绝望 我宁愿要梅毒
Disappointing. I put in for syphilis.
别笑了 我穿着这玩意儿拿着27杯橙汁
Stop laughing. I have to carry 27 juices
走了两条街
2 blocks wearing this.
为啥你要让那个狗娘这么和你说话?
Why'd you let the dog lady talk to you like that?
她是我朋友 即使穿着那种衣服
She's my friend, even in that shirt.
嗯 又花了12刀
Well, there goes another $12.
我在这衣服上花的钱比我在
I have spent more money dry cleaning this blouse
医疗保健上花的更多
Than I have on health care.
医疗保健? 你是说我们在99分店买的
Health care? You mean that box of band-aids
创可贴盒?
We got at the 99 cent store?
明天我得打扮好点
I just have to look good tomorrow.
今天真是惨不忍睹
Today was mortifying.
卖果汁地方的人叫我"倒霉犬"
They called me "sad dog" at the juice place.
"倒霉犬 你的果汁好了"
"Sad dog, your juices are ready."
倒霉犬 上菜
Sad dog, pick up.
你能把这些端到10号桌吗? 我在这儿支援你
Can you take these to table ten? I'm backed up on the booths.
你能吗? 我只在这里坐了一分钟
Can you? I'm kind of just sitting here a minute,
享受着不必被人指手划脚
Enjoying not being told what to do.
我在学校受够了
I get enough of it at that school.
看
Look.
如果你想要做出丰功伟绩 就好好做
If you're gonna do the martyr thing, do it right.
把你的手放进滚烫的油里
Stick your hand in boiling oil
要么更痛苦的事 放任自己收看
or even more painful, binge-watch
Bravo台的炫富真人秀"国王的日落"
Shahs of sunset on bravo.
咱们去厨房 我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you in the kitchen now.
赶紧走 有人要因学校的事而挨训了
Leave, someone's about to get schooled about school.
听起来下流又肮脏
This looks like it's going to get dirty and ugly.
我能拍下来吗?
May I film it?
如果可以的话 我可以放到网上卖吗?
And if so, may I then sell it on the internet?
听着 你不用这样为我的
Look. You can't just do this for me.
没错 所以我们退出?
You're right. So we're out?
不 我们不能退出 你说过你会为了我而去做
No, we're not out, you said you were gonna do this for me.
我知道 但你刚刚说了
I know, but you just said
我不用这样为你
I can't just do it for you,
而我同意
And I agree.
我这是在逗谁啊?
I mean, who was I kidding?
我 你在逗我
Me. You were kidding me.
我去那里工作 想着利用我的
I went in there thinking I was gonna use
生意必杀技 还揣着希望
My business skills, and whatever hope
要和那位法国帅哥调情
I had of a flirtation with frenchie mcfrench
结果他一看到窗外
Went out the window when he saw me
就发现我穿着那件T裇 暗示着
Wearing that t-shirt that said,
"别忘了帮我阉割手术"
"don't forget to spay and neuter me."
好吧 我退出 没问题
Fine, I can quit. It's fine.
- 是吗? 真的吗?  - 不 不好
- It is? Really?  - No, it's not fine.
- 我在逗谁呢?  - 我 你在逗我
- Who am I kidding?  - Me. You were kidding me.
好吧 你得想办法
Well, you've gotta figure out something there
保持兴趣 你不能只为了我
To keep you interested, because you can't go
才去糕点学校
To pastry school just for me,
而我也不会因为你 而不去学校
And I'm not gonna not go to pastry school for you.
Max 你是对的
Okay. You're right, Max.
为了你我会去的
Of course I'll do it for you.
我今天很悲催
I just had a bad day.
我们俩都很悲催
I mean, we both did.
你没了那个男士公文包和毒品
You lost your man's briefcase and your drugs,
我丢了自尊和可能的艳遇
and I lost my dignity and a possible love interest.
惊喜!
Surprise!
看 就该这样的
See, that's how it's supposed to go.
我们再送你一新书包
We got you a new book bag.
对 还有一件新厨师袍
Yeah, and a new chef's jacket.
以及一把弹簧刀
And a switchblade.
对 因为我们没办法再买一件厨师袍
Yeah, cause we're not buying another chef's jacket.
Max 你懂这是意味着什么吗
Max, you know what this means?
是我得了两个惊喜 而你一无所获?
That I got two surprises, and you got nothing?
不 这说明学校的事情都能解决
No, that everything's gonna work out at that school.
我是说 一眨眼的功夫
I mean, in the blink of an eye,
就像这样 万事都能
just like this, things can change
否极泰来
from bad to good.
当然也没那么好 他们还是
Well, not totally good. They still haven't
没给我什么东西
gotten me anything.
Caroline 你不是什么都没有
Caroline, you didn't not get anything.
瞧 你的独家铅笔盒
Here, your very own pencil case.
不过这次没笔了 那老板被抓了
But no pencils. My pencil dealer got busted.
啊 谢谢大家
Aw. Thank you, guys.
我好感动 我真没想到
I'm touched. I was not expecting it.
是吗? 因为我们可是被你逼着送礼物的
Really?  Cause you kinda bullied us all into it.
我口语得了780分
So that's a 780 on verbal,
数学780分
and a 780 on math.
还有我的金融课也一样
And with my degree in Finance,
现在却要我挤在城里去买果汁
jackass-ing around the city getting juice
真是浪费我的才华
could be seen as a waste of my talents.
当时我在毕业典礼上说过...
And as the valedictorian at my graduation said...
抛开现在的我
And I'm stealing from myself here,
"我预见了金融的未来
"I've seen the future of Finance,
我们就是未来 "
and it's us."
所以你要我去端果汁吗?
So you want me to get the juices?
就今天 拜托?
Just for today. Please?
制作蛋白酥皮饼是一种简单的
Meringue cookies are a simple way
训练我们的糕点技术的方法
to practice our pastry bag technique.
主厨 你掌握了一种有趣的技术
Hm, interesting technique you got going there, chef.
哥们 我们把抛弃自己无聊的搭档
Dude, we gotta ditch these deadbeat partners.
我被困着要和一大妈同组
I'm stuck over there with grandma.
不要 我现在跟旁边这大家伙一组
No, I'm staying with the big guy next to me.
他不会给我惹麻烦
He's not gonna get me in trouble.
他从不说话 你快走开
He never talks. Get outta here.
"胖子阿伯特"主角是一名肥胖的黑人
回你的位置上 胖子阿伯特
Go back to your own table, fat Albert.
好
Okay.
我回去
I'm going back.
你叫我胖子阿伯特 是因为我是黑人
And the fat Albert thing was cause I'm black,
而不是指我胖 对吧?
Not fat, right?
因为我一年会去健身两三次
Cause I go to the gym two, three times a year.
我只听见你俩讲话 而不是烘焙
I hear talking, but no baking up front.
不 不 你只听见烘焙声
No, no, no, you only hear baking.
我们只是在疯狂的学习烘焙
Just furiously master-baking up here.
蛋白酥皮需要做出漂亮的峰
The meringue needs to have nice peaks.
你要尽量做出柔软潮湿 尖挺的峰
You are looking to make moist, pointy peaks.
我喜欢捏它们
I like to pinch them.
老师 说真的 咱们男人间说话
Chef, seriously, man-to-man,
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
我觉得Max不应该跟那个大家伙一组
I don't think Max should be stuck with that big guy.
他人可不行
He's not cool.
我刚才在那边 而那男的
I was just over there, and the only
唯一感兴趣的高峰 是她的那对
pointy peaks he's interested in are hers.
老师 我指的是胸
Talkin' boobies here, chef.
John 厨师Deke觉得
Chef John, chef Deke here
你似乎是在性骚扰Max
seems to think you are sexually harassing Max.
哦 拜托
Oh, please.
如果我想骚扰谁 老师 那一定是你哦
If I was harassing anyone, it would be you, chef.
别逗了
I mean, come on.
我一会儿回来 男同志
Be right back, big Mary.
你懂的
You know it.
我的果汁呢? 都一个小时了
Where's my juice? It's been an hour.
那个情绪波动的姑娘去拿了
The mood swing elf's getting them.
听着 我一会要进去
Look, I'm coming in there
跟Nicholas厨师长调情 当我进去时
to flirt with chef Nicholas, and when I enter,
我要你说 "Caroline 你好靓啊 "
i need you to say, "Caroline, you look amazing."
不要
No.
我真说不出来
I actually physically can't say that.
我宁愿走进去大叫
I would rather walk in there and yell,
"我有大螃蟹 其中有三个逃了"
"i have crabs, and three of them just escaped."
快报警 快报警
Call 9...1...1. Call 9...1...1.
那个可爱的混血儿出事了
Something's happened to the adorable mixed-race one.
Deke吗?
Deke?
他有糖尿病 需要注射胰岛素
He's Diabetic. He needs insulin.
这儿谁会注射?
Has anyone here ever administered a needle?
注射跟"打进去"是同一回事 对吧?
Uh, administer means the same thing as "shove it in," right?
好 好 Max 来 快来
Good, good, good, Max. Come, come, come.
好 他的针管在腰包里
Okay, uh, his syringes are in his fanny pack.
我还从未试过 在没有
I've actually never done this
铁娘子乐队的背景音乐下玩注射
without Iron maiden playing in the background,
我要打针了
but I'll give it a shot.
随便打在我的魔鬼身材上
Just put it anywhere in my hot bod.
老天保佑
God help us.
噢 我怕针头 我不看了
Oh, I hate needles. I can't look.
噢
Oh.
赶紧收拾去啊 女人们
Get it together, ladies.
这也是别人不给我抱孩子的原因
This is why I'm not allowed to hold babies.
Max 从现在起
Max, I think you and Deke
你和Deke做搭档
should be Lab partners from now on
以防万一有类似事情发生
in case something like this happens again.
- 好吗?  - 这必须的
- Is that okay?  - I guess if I have to.
Max呢?
Max?
那必须的
I guess if I have to.
你是故意不打胰岛素的吗?
What, did you not take your insulin on purpose?
我超想成你搭档
I really wanted to be your partner.
Bebe 在这里我找不到厨师袍
Bebe, I can't find a chef jacket anywhere in here.
还有抱歉 我知道我不能穿这种袍子
And I'm sorry, I know I'm not supposed to wear one,
但我好冷 我无法一整天
but I'm really cold, and I can't walk around
带着这一身脏
like this all day.
也许我能帮上忙
Maybe I can help.
你不能又湿又冷地站在这里
You can't stand there wet and cold.
- 把我的外套拿去  - 哦 不 不行
- Take my jacket.  - Oh, no, no, no.
你不必... 哦 这件也行
You don't have... oh, that'll work.
抱歉我里面没穿衣服
I'm sorry about the no shirt under,
但我刚上课上得挺热的
but I just get so hot when I'm teaching.
嗯 是热 太热辣了
Yeah, hot. So hot.
哦 我的妈妈咪啊
Oh mon dieu.
我刚把衣服给Caroline
I was just giving it to Caroline.
我是说 她要换件衣服
I mean, she needs something to wear,
还... 还有现在她有衣服了
and... and now, she has it.
同学 一会见
Chef, I will see you later.
还有Caroline哦
Caroline.
Max 我想我找到让我感兴趣的了
Max, I think I found something to keep me interested.
真是奇怪 我现在成了好学生吗
This is weird. So I'm the good student now?
而你成了跟老师上床的坏学生?
And you're the one sleeping with the teacher?
我们不会上床的
We're not sleeping together.
那啥? 你觉得他想吗?
Why? Do you think he wants to?
这我不知道 不过你得
I don't know, but you better hurry it up
赶在那个男同之前下手
before big Mary gets him.